ILR School Communications Department Director's Files /4264
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Communications Department Director's Files
1976-1991
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
/4264
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records (documents), case files.
6181605
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4264 P: ILR School Communications Department Photographs /4264 PUBS: ILR School Communications Department Publications
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Communications Department
6181605
- Publicity 1990, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Publicity 1989 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Publicity 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- New Release 1987 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Albany Lists: Invitations, Mailings, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Albany Press (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Union Research Dirs., 1988 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Media, 1985-1988 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Radio Spots 10/80, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Video Tapes, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- PBS, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- US Postal Service, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Stationery, Logos, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- School Publications, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Brochures, 1985-1987 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- AFL-CIO Speech '88, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Ehrenberg: Compensation Conference, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- ILR: Access, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Press Releases 40th Anniversary, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 40th Anniversary Publications, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Fortieth Anniversary SP'87, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Industrial and Labor Relations at Cornell University (Aug. '84), 1984 (Box 1, Folder 22)